Guide to the North Carolina Farm Bureau Records
North Carolina Farm Bureau Records
- Audiovisual Materials, 1960-1999; 3.5 linear feet
  - Videocassettes
    - "Flue Cured Farm Bailing" (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - "Trouble in the Hen House" (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - "Cattle Handling and Transportation" (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - "Tobacco: Helping Youth Say No" (3 Copies) (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - "Meatpacker Concentration and Vertical Integration" (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - "Now More Than Ever" (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - "AFBF Cattle/Hog Forum" (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - "Oilseed Dilemma" (2 Copies) (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - "Farm Bill Sign Up Conference" (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - "The Bi-Rotor Story" (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - "Tennessee Livestock Cattle Sale" (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - "The Smart Solution" (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - "National Pork Producers- Report to Investors" (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - "X-Ray of Tobacco Samples" (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - "1996-1997 Flue-Cured Tobacco Situation" (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - "Cotton Production" (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - "Swine Handling and Transportation" (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - "Spindle Picker Harvesting" (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - "Texas Program" (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - "1986 Peanut Outlook" (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - "Peanut Grower Promotion Meeting" (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - "Price Risk Management" (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - "1999 Carolina Farm Show" (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - "Flue-Cured Farm Bailing" (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Ag in the Classroom videocasette, possible oral histories. 2009 Presidents address from Convention, New Employee Training, 1985 (Box 136)
- Artifacts, 0.5 linear feet
  The artifacts series is comprised of a variety of items compiled by the Farm Bureau during the history of their organization. The majority of the artifacts are pins awarded to Farm Bureau members. Other items include guest books from Farm Bureau events and framed memorabilia.
  - Brolier Program Tie Bar (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Silver Tie Bar (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Silver Button (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Charm (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - North Carolina Farm Bureau Button (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - 2 Guest Books signed at North Carolina Farm Bureau Building Dedication, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Framed Copy of 1942 Congressional Record testifying "Who the Farm Bureau Works For" (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Additions, 1936-1989, undated; 1936 1989; 1 linear feet
  This series contains correspondence, reports, meeting notes, committee and board minutes, brochures, press releases and clippings, and other items related to both the North Carolina Farm Bureau and other farm organizations, including the American Farm Bureau Federation. These materials have been arranged by type of material except where topical arrangement was more efficient.
  - Correspondence, 1962-1989, undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1936, 1963-1983, undated (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1971-1983, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Reports, 1961-1977, undated (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Meetings, 1953-1988, undated (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Committees and Boards, 1936, 1953-1989 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Financial Records, 1953-1986 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Brochures, 1952-1988 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases and Clippings, 1937, 1967-1972 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Legislation and Legal Action, 1967-1982 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Tobacco, 1953-1978 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1982, undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1949-1984, undated (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Born digital materials (disks, etc.) (Carton 145)